[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of wolf is White Fang from Jack Londons popular novel White Fang?", "correct_answer": "Wolf hybrid", "incorrect_answers": ["Grey wolf", "White wolf", "Red wolf"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which cooking technique is considered to be best for preserving vitamins and minerals in meat and fish, during heat processing?", "correct_answer": "Roasting", "incorrect_answers": ["Deep frying", "Braising", "Sauteing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "2006 is the year of this sign, described as a noble and honest creature.", "correct_answer": "Dog", "incorrect_answers": ["Ox", "Pig", "Horse"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Humans have 33 permanent teeth.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the derivative of y in this function related to the exponential constant e: If y=e^x?", "correct_answer": "e^x", "incorrect_answers": ["e^x +x", "e^pi", "e"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of meat is used for the preparation of the traditional Indonesian dish called Betutu?", "correct_answer": "Chicken", "incorrect_answers": ["Pork", "Beef", "Lamb"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This moon, bearing the name of the ferryman of the dead in Greek mythology, is the largest satellite of Pluto.", "correct_answer": "Charon", "incorrect_answers": ["Nereid", "Proteus", "Larissa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Anchorman, Brian Fantana attempts to hit on Veronica.  What special cologne does he apply for this occasion?", "correct_answer": "Sex Panther", "incorrect_answers": ["Bohemian Musk", "Blackbeards Delight", "London Gentleman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Barista?", "correct_answer": "The Italian word for bartender", "incorrect_answers": ["The term applied to an expert coffee roaster", "The French word for attorney", "The proprietor of a coffee shop"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following powers the time machine featured in the movie Back to the Future?", "correct_answer": "Plutonium", "incorrect_answers": ["Lithium battery", "Regular unleaded gas", "Diesel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the color theory what should red paint look viewed under blue light?", "correct_answer": "Black", "incorrect_answers": ["Transparent", "White", "Purple"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is alektorophobia?", "correct_answer": "The unreasonable fear of chickens", "incorrect_answers": ["The unreasonable fear of birds of prey", "The unreasonable fear of roaches", "The unreasonable fear of sharks"]}]